

CONTACT

435.881.4520

holladaystudio@gmail.com

2115 S 2000 E Salt Lake City, UT 84106

jadenholladay.com

ABOUT

Hi, I'm Jaden Holladay, and I'm currently a student of the Entertainment Arts & Engineering (EAE) program at the University of Utah. Adobe featured me in a story titled "Jaden Holladay, developing limitless creativity" where I demonstrated diverse talents. I have spent time developing web applications, and mobile/computer games. Several games I have created achieved top 10 in popularity on Blizzard Entertainment's Starcraft II Arcade. As a software engineer, I specialize in tools and network programming.

Jaden Holladay

Software engineer with a passion for games.

TECHNICAL SKILLS -

- · C++, C, C#, Python, JavaScript, x86
- · Unity 3D, Unreal Engine
- · NodeJS, ExpressJS, GraphQL
- TCP/UDP/Websockets
- · Linear Algebra, Calculus, Discrete Math
- · ReactJS, Flux Architecture

- · Adobe Creative Cloud
- Graphic Design (Illustrator)
- · Scrum & Agile Development
- · Git & SVN
- · Postgresql, NoSQL
- · Visual Studio, Emacs, Atom

SELECTED PROJECTS -

BRANCHING NODE EDITOR | LEAD PROGRAMMER

· Visual tool for building branching narratives.

· Communicates with a GraphQL/NodeJS Server.

THE IRREGULAR | LEAD PROGRAMMER

• Finalist in the Department of Education's EdSim Challenge.

2016-Present

· Virtual Reality Game built with Unity.

ADOBE STUDENT FEATURE | STUDENT

• Featured in a story; "Jaden Holladay, developing limitless creativity".

2015

2017

· Video & Article viewable at jadenholladay.com/adobe.

MARINE ARENA 2 | GAMEPLAY PROGRAMMER

• Top 10 in Blizzard Entertainments' Starcraft 2 Arcade.

2014

· Mod built for Blizzard Entertainments' Starcraft 2.

WORK EXPERIENCE —

TECHNICAL DIRECTOR

Octothorpe

2015-Present

WEB ENGINEER

Atomic Jolt

2014-2015

CHAMBER COORDINATOR

Cache Chamber of Commerce

2014

EDUCATION -

UNIVERSITY OF UTAH

B.S. Computer Science Entertainment Arts & Engineering Emphasis 2012-2019